<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Misa&#39;s Odekake Blog</title>
    <link>https://odekake.zzzmisa.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Misa&#39;s Odekake Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://odekake.zzzmisa.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Everlast, an endlessly reusable notebook</title>
      <link>https://odekake.zzzmisa.com/everlast_notebook/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://odekake.zzzmisa.com/everlast_notebook/</guid>
      <description>The reason why I bought I bought an Everlast notebook made by Rocketbook! I had been searching for paperless life. This is the video which made me decide to get the notebook when I saw at first sight.
  The points I thought nice  I can erase many times and use endlessly. I can erase using wet tissue: the item is in office. It is easy to convert to a digital format.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Amagasaki Factory Night View</title>
      <link>https://odekake.zzzmisa.com/amagasaki-factory-night-view/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://odekake.zzzmisa.com/amagasaki-factory-night-view/</guid>
      <description>I went to a photo shoot at a factory in Amagasaki tonight. If you search on the internet, you will be able to see more photos with cool, stunning views. However, they just make a good shot! In fact the scenery was not as glittering as the typical photos. I also did my best to take the sparkling photos.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Toro Nagashi Festival at Hirosawa Pond</title>
      <link>https://odekake.zzzmisa.com/toro-nagashi-festival-in-hirosawa-pond/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://odekake.zzzmisa.com/toro-nagashi-festival-in-hirosawa-pond/</guid>
      <description>Toro Nagashi Festival at Hirosawa Pond At night on August 16th, I went to Hirosawa Pond to see the Toro Nagashi Festival. This Japanese traditional festival takes place every year for sending off ancestors&#39; spirit. Many colorful lanterns were floating over the water. It was considerably beautiful!! Similar festival is held near Togetsukyo Bridge over Katsura River. However, I was told the festival at the pond is more fantastic than</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Azuchi Castle Ruins</title>
      <link>https://odekake.zzzmisa.com/azuchi-castle/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://odekake.zzzmisa.com/azuchi-castle/</guid>
      <description>Azuchi Castle Ruins. This was the castle of famous feudal warlord Nobunaga Oda. There are only stone walls and stairs were left, but I guess it is what is called decadentism, the place has a nice atmosphere. From the tower ruin, you can overlook the townscape and the lakescape.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kawachi Wind Cave</title>
      <link>https://odekake.zzzmisa.com/kawachi-wind-cave/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://odekake.zzzmisa.com/kawachi-wind-cave/</guid>
      <description>I entered Kawachi Wind Cave. The inside of the cave is very cool regardless of summer! I thought there is likely Blue Grotto, Italy, but underground lake was keep out area. Well, it was nice to feel the power of nature even just in the public open area.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Aging fish restaurant Tai-no-tai</title>
      <link>https://odekake.zzzmisa.com/tai-no-tai/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://odekake.zzzmisa.com/tai-no-tai/</guid>
      <description>I had known that aging meat is a trend, but this night I went to eat the aging fish. I thought&amp;hellip;it might be stale!? According to a shop flyer, temperature control is very difficult, so aging management is done by chefs. I do not want to try this at home. I didn&amp;rsquo;t understand what the difference between fresh fish and aging fish, was but both were delicious!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Takoyaki restaurant Takonotetsu</title>
      <link>https://odekake.zzzmisa.com/takonotetsu/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://odekake.zzzmisa.com/takonotetsu/</guid>
      <description>I was with guests from Tokyo, so we ate Takoyaki which is a local food in Osaka. As far as I know, in the Umeda area (around Osaka station), only the &amp;ldquo;Takonotetsu&amp;rdquo; (Takoyaki restaurant) enables us to roast Takoyaki by ourselves. There are two Takonotetsu in the Umeda area. The Takonotetsu I went to is the Marubiru Shop. When I checked in the dictionary, the English name of Takoyaki is</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yuge Farm</title>
      <link>https://odekake.zzzmisa.com/yuge-farm/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://odekake.zzzmisa.com/yuge-farm/</guid>
      <description>I went to the Yuge Farm in the northern Kobe. We can see cows closely in the farm. When I visited, there was a baby cow which was born a week before. I was surprised that he was great in size in spite of being only one week old. Then, the milk there was very very delicious! It was quite different from the one in grocery stores. Besides, different from</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hydrangea field in Ohno Alps land</title>
      <link>https://odekake.zzzmisa.com/hydrangea-field-in-ohno-alps-land/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://odekake.zzzmisa.com/hydrangea-field-in-ohno-alps-land/</guid>
      <description>I went for a trip to enjoy seeing a &amp;ldquo;Hygandrea&amp;rdquo; field at the top of Mt. Ohno in Inagawa town. We arrived there by car, however the road was narrow and the fog was terrible that day, so we drove carefully. Hyndrangeas during fog are nice too look at and the atmosphere seems to be so calm. The best season for flowers is on June and July, but I heard</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Aramaki Rose Park</title>
      <link>https://odekake.zzzmisa.com/aramaki-rose-park/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://odekake.zzzmisa.com/aramaki-rose-park/</guid>
      <description>I went to Aramaki Rose Park by bicycle. A lot of different roses were blooming in the large and splendid park. Admission is free. Isn’t it something!? Sprinkler&amp;rsquo;s water splashed when watering time. Children were excited getting wet. I almost got wet too. I recommend families with children to bring spare clothes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tatsuta Jam</title>
      <link>https://odekake.zzzmisa.com/tatsuta-jam/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://odekake.zzzmisa.com/tatsuta-jam/</guid>
      <description>I visited Tatsuta Jam which was selected as the top five in the world&amp;rsquo;s Dalemain Marmalade Awards 2016. It is a lovely shop that has a cat design signboard. Unfortunately, the &amp;ldquo;yuzu marmalade&amp;rdquo; which won the prize are sold out in this season, so I bought an amanatsu marmalade jam. These jams are perfect for gifts because of it&amp;rsquo;s cute packaging and long shelf life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Great Zelkova Tree of Noma</title>
      <link>https://odekake.zzzmisa.com/great-zelkova-tree-of-noma/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://odekake.zzzmisa.com/great-zelkova-tree-of-noma/</guid>
      <description>I just went to Noma No Ookeyaki (Great Zelkova Tree Of Noma) to see the brown hawk-owl today. Brown hawk-owl comes there to lay eggs between late March to mid May and Ural owl, between mid May to last July. Good roasted coffee was sold very nearby, so I have drunk it and I was relaxed seeing the big tree.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Okunoshima &#34;Rabbit Island&#34;</title>
      <link>https://odekake.zzzmisa.com/okunoshima-island/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://odekake.zzzmisa.com/okunoshima-island/</guid>
      <description>I went to Okunoshima known as &amp;ldquo;Rabbit Island&amp;rdquo;. To the island, ships are in service from the mainland or Omishima Island in Shimanami Kaido Line, and I crossed over from the latter. Many rabbits live on the island, so tourists enjoy with rabbits such as giving food and taking pictures. They are wild, but very friendly! The size of island is small, so on foot is enough to looking around.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mino Fall</title>
      <link>https://odekake.zzzmisa.com/mino-fall/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://odekake.zzzmisa.com/mino-fall/</guid>
      <description>I went to see Mino fall. The way from the station was a good hiking course for me who haven&amp;rsquo;t had much exercise. I feel the impact of the monkies was bigger than the fall. The international visitor sat on the bench, he took his eyes off, in the next moment a bag of snack in his tote bag was stolen by monkey!! I was scary whether I was also</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tojinbo Cliffs</title>
      <link>https://odekake.zzzmisa.com/tojinbo-cliffs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Sep 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://odekake.zzzmisa.com/tojinbo-cliffs/</guid>
      <description>Speaking of the place where the criminals are cornered by detectives in Japanese suspense dramas is Tojinbo. It is sightseeing spot cliffs on the sea. I went there. We can watch the cliffs from above, but I was afraid, so I didn&amp;rsquo;t get too close. If I carelessly fall down, I will possibly die. Then, I decided to take a boat tour, and I watched the cliffs from below. The</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cafe Poko no Mori, a cafe where you can meet birds</title>
      <link>https://odekake.zzzmisa.com/torimi-cafe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Sep 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://odekake.zzzmisa.com/torimi-cafe/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Torimi&amp;rdquo; means bird watching. We can meet many kinds of small birds. It is near Oji Zoo. We went there after visiting the zoo. Touching birds wasn&amp;rsquo;t allowed in this cafe, unlike other bird cafes. However, through the glass, birds came near me! My favorite type of birds is cockatiels, but he was very active and restless, so it was difficult to take pictures. Both drinks and sweets were related</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Owl Café Crew, a café where you can touch owls</title>
      <link>https://odekake.zzzmisa.com/owl-cafe-crew/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Jun 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://odekake.zzzmisa.com/owl-cafe-crew/</guid>
      <description>I had a dinner at Owl Café, which is called Owl Café Crew, in Mino City. I wondered if owls are nocturnal and are more active at night, so I visited at dinner. I rubbed them! It was fluffy! I was satisfied with not only the owls but also the foods The galette was unusual meal for me and it tasted so good.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About me</title>
      <link>https://odekake.zzzmisa.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://odekake.zzzmisa.com/about/</guid>
      <description>This is a blog that introduces my recommended spots. Since I live in the Hokusetsu area in Osaka, I mainly introduce around there. I am studying English, so I try to make time to write a diary in English. Please correct my English, if it&amp;rsquo;s wrong. Feel free to contact me on Twitter or Contact Form. My name: Misa Occupation: Engineer (Web developer, App developper, Data analyst) Favorite things: Studying</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
