<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Osaka Pref. on Misa's Odekake Blog</title><link>https://odekake.zzzmisa.com/tags/osaka-pref./</link><description>Recent content in Osaka Pref. on Misa's Odekake Blog</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://odekake.zzzmisa.com/tags/osaka-pref./index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Aging fish restaurant Tai-no-tai</title><link>https://odekake.zzzmisa.com/tai-no-tai/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://odekake.zzzmisa.com/tai-no-tai/</guid><description>I had known that aging meat is a trend, but this night I went to eat the aging fish. I thought&amp;hellip;it might be stale!? According to a shop flyer, temperature control is very difficult, so aging management is done by chefs. I do not want to try this at home. I didn&amp;rsquo;t understand what the difference between fresh fish and aging fish, was but both were delicious!</description></item><item><title>Takoyaki restaurant Takonotetsu</title><link>https://odekake.zzzmisa.com/takonotetsu/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://odekake.zzzmisa.com/takonotetsu/</guid><description>I was with guests from Tokyo, so we ate Takoyaki which is a local food in Osaka. As far as I know, in the Umeda area (around Osaka station), only the &amp;ldquo;Takonotetsu&amp;rdquo; (Takoyaki restaurant) enables us to roast Takoyaki by ourselves. There are two Takonotetsu in the Umeda area. The Takonotetsu I went to is the Marubiru Shop. When I checked in the dictionary, the English name of Takoyaki is</description></item><item><title>Tatsuta Jam</title><link>https://odekake.zzzmisa.com/tatsuta-jam/</link><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://odekake.zzzmisa.com/tatsuta-jam/</guid><description>I visited Tatsuta Jam which was selected as the top five in the world&amp;rsquo;s Dalemain Marmalade Awards 2016. It is a lovely shop that has a cat design signboard. Unfortunately, the &amp;ldquo;yuzu marmalade&amp;rdquo; which won the prize are sold out in this season, so I bought an amanatsu marmalade jam. These jams are perfect for gifts because of it&amp;rsquo;s cute packaging and long shelf life.</description></item><item><title>Great Zelkova Tree of Noma</title><link>https://odekake.zzzmisa.com/great-zelkova-tree-of-noma/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://odekake.zzzmisa.com/great-zelkova-tree-of-noma/</guid><description>I just went to Noma No Ookeyaki (Great Zelkova Tree Of Noma) to see the brown hawk-owl today. Brown hawk-owl comes there to lay eggs between late March to mid May and Ural owl, between mid May to last July. Good roasted coffee was sold very nearby, so I have drunk it and I was relaxed seeing the big tree.</description></item><item><title>Mino Fall</title><link>https://odekake.zzzmisa.com/mino-fall/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://odekake.zzzmisa.com/mino-fall/</guid><description>I went to see Mino fall. The way from the station was a good hiking course for me who haven&amp;rsquo;t had much exercise. I feel the impact of the monkies was bigger than the fall. The international visitor sat on the bench, he took his eyes off, in the next moment a bag of snack in his tote bag was stolen by monkey!! I was scary whether I was also</description></item><item><title>Owl Café Crew, a café where you can touch owls</title><link>https://odekake.zzzmisa.com/owl-cafe-crew/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jun 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://odekake.zzzmisa.com/owl-cafe-crew/</guid><description>I had a dinner at Owl Café, which is called Owl Café Crew, in Mino City. I wondered if owls are nocturnal and are more active at night, so I visited at dinner. I rubbed them! It was fluffy! I was satisfied with not only the owls but also the foods The galette was unusual meal for me and it tasted so good.</description></item></channel></rss>