<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Bird on Misa&#39;s Odekake Blog</title>
    <link>https://odekake.zzzmisa.com/tags/bird/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Bird on Misa&#39;s Odekake Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://odekake.zzzmisa.com/tags/bird/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Great Zelkova Tree of Noma</title>
      <link>https://odekake.zzzmisa.com/great-zelkova-tree-of-noma/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://odekake.zzzmisa.com/great-zelkova-tree-of-noma/</guid>
      <description>I just went to Noma No Ookeyaki (Great Zelkova Tree Of Noma) to see the brown hawk-owl today. Brown hawk-owl comes there to lay eggs between late March to mid May and Ural owl, between mid May to last July. Good roasted coffee was sold very nearby, so I have drunk it and I was relaxed seeing the big tree.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cafe Poko no Mori, a cafe where you can meet birds</title>
      <link>https://odekake.zzzmisa.com/torimi-cafe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Sep 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://odekake.zzzmisa.com/torimi-cafe/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Torimi&amp;rdquo; means bird watching. We can meet many kinds of small birds. It is near Oji Zoo. We went there after visiting the zoo. Touching birds wasn&amp;rsquo;t allowed in this cafe, unlike other bird cafes. However, through the glass, birds came near me! My favorite type of birds is cockatiels, but he was very active and restless, so it was difficult to take pictures. Both drinks and sweets were related</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Owl Café Crew, a café where you can touch owls</title>
      <link>https://odekake.zzzmisa.com/owl-cafe-crew/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Jun 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://odekake.zzzmisa.com/owl-cafe-crew/</guid>
      <description>I had a dinner at Owl Café, which is called Owl Café Crew, in Mino City. I wondered if owls are nocturnal and are more active at night, so I visited at dinner. I rubbed them! It was fluffy! I was satisfied with not only the owls but also the foods The galette was unusual meal for me and it tasted so good.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
