<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Hyogo Pref. on Misa&#39;s Odekake Blog</title>
    <link>https://odekake.zzzmisa.com/tags/hyogo-pref./</link>
    <description>Recent content in Hyogo Pref. on Misa&#39;s Odekake Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://odekake.zzzmisa.com/tags/hyogo-pref./index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Amagasaki Factory Night View</title>
      <link>https://odekake.zzzmisa.com/amagasaki-factory-night-view/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://odekake.zzzmisa.com/amagasaki-factory-night-view/</guid>
      <description>I went to a photo shoot at a factory in Amagasaki tonight. If you search on the internet, you will be able to see more photos with cool, stunning views. However, they just make a good shot! In fact the scenery was not as glittering as the typical photos. I also did my best to take the sparkling photos.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yuge Farm</title>
      <link>https://odekake.zzzmisa.com/yuge-farm/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://odekake.zzzmisa.com/yuge-farm/</guid>
      <description>I went to the Yuge Farm in the northern Kobe. We can see cows closely in the farm. When I visited, there was a baby cow which was born a week before. I was surprised that he was great in size in spite of being only one week old. Then, the milk there was very very delicious! It was quite different from the one in grocery stores. Besides, different from</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hydrangea field in Ohno Alps land</title>
      <link>https://odekake.zzzmisa.com/hydrangea-field-in-ohno-alps-land/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://odekake.zzzmisa.com/hydrangea-field-in-ohno-alps-land/</guid>
      <description>I went for a trip to enjoy seeing a &amp;ldquo;Hygandrea&amp;rdquo; field at the top of Mt. Ohno in Inagawa town. We arrived there by car, however the road was narrow and the fog was terrible that day, so we drove carefully. Hyndrangeas during fog are nice too look at and the atmosphere seems to be so calm. The best season for flowers is on June and July, but I heard</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Aramaki Rose Park</title>
      <link>https://odekake.zzzmisa.com/aramaki-rose-park/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://odekake.zzzmisa.com/aramaki-rose-park/</guid>
      <description>I went to Aramaki Rose Park by bicycle. A lot of different roses were blooming in the large and splendid park. Admission is free. Isn’t it something!? Sprinkler&amp;rsquo;s water splashed when watering time. Children were excited getting wet. I almost got wet too. I recommend families with children to bring spare clothes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cafe Poko no Mori, a cafe where you can meet birds</title>
      <link>https://odekake.zzzmisa.com/torimi-cafe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Sep 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://odekake.zzzmisa.com/torimi-cafe/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Torimi&amp;rdquo; means bird watching. We can meet many kinds of small birds. It is near Oji Zoo. We went there after visiting the zoo. Touching birds wasn&amp;rsquo;t allowed in this cafe, unlike other bird cafes. However, through the glass, birds came near me! My favorite type of birds is cockatiels, but he was very active and restless, so it was difficult to take pictures. Both drinks and sweets were related</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>